Guide to the William Shockley Papers SC0222
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2007-198
  - Audiovisual material
    - Audiorecordings
      - (Th), Side A: cont Will Hurst III; Troxler of 601; Schneer / Side B: Troxler; re Kuttner, 1973 Aug 15-16; 92.11.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (Th), Side A: cont. R.E. Kuttner; Kenneth Sharp; Sec to Mrs. Troxler; Al Wang / Side B: Troxler; Moral Post.; Christian Eugenics Soc; Dysgenics; Invite Letter; Drugs and Alc. [alter given?], 1973 Aug 16-18; 92.11.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (Th), Side A: cont Troxler; RT Osborne; Bill Loeb / Side B: RT Osorne; Audrey [Shuey?], 1973 Aug 18-19; 92.11.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (Th), Side A: cont A. Shuey; Herb Levy; KRON / Side B: Troxler; Wang; AP & OREM; [SFex + SJMerc?]; Osborne; Linda Parets; Parets KHJ, 1973 Jul 19-22; 92.11.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (C), Lunch Sticknetys OREM + Hainstock, 1973 Aug 21; 92.11.12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (Th), Side A: Parets re R-Con; Orem; John Schwartz re Farunato; KRON; Levy; Almena Lomax / Side B: [Blank?], 1973 Aug 22; 92.12.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (Th), Side A: Almena Lomax; Wang; Penny Hainstock / Side B: Dick [Gauthier?]; Parets; ARJ; Osborne; Clack-Texas, 1973 Aug 22-26; 92.12.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - Warden KQED Ch 9 Received, 1973 Aug 24; 92.12.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (Th)(TV), Side A: Parets; ARJ; Wang; Warden / Side B: Wang; Howard Brownstein; Hod. Law School Forum, 1973 Aug 24-29; 92.12.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (C), Side A: Troxler Lunch / Side B: Lunch at Birmingham "Club"; cont McEdward Nolan; John Troxler; Travis Osborne, 1973 Aug 24; 92.12.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (C), Side A: ELS on Terence O'Flaherty + Interview Leonard Chamblee Post Herald / Side B: [illegible], 1973 Aug 24; 92.12.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (L), 76th St. Presbyt. Church, 1973 Aug 24; 92.12.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (C)(L), Side A: Post Lect disc [Truslian?] B. News; Field Negro Casey / Side B: Osborne Dinner; Troxler breakfast [Casey sterilize males] circassian; Brkfst talk; McGurk; Casey on Nobel + [illegible], 1973 Aug 24-25; 92.12.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (C), At Breakfast Post Troxler Lecture, 1973 Aug 25; 92.12.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (C), Side A: Post Breakfast discussion; Jessup, McEdward Nolen; McGurk "[Primate?] Brain" / Side B: [Couklin?], 1973 Aug 25; 92.12.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (T)(C), Side A: [Couklin Rid; Neesmith; Notary; Neesmith (Lions Club); Dixon; Mrs. Dixon; Director Administration MCA "Recipients"; Notary Procedure / Side B: Dixon; Yarborough; Neesmith; Frank McGurk, 1973 Aug 25-26; 92.12.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 92)
      - (T,C) Side A: Frank McGurk, Troxler, Gov's Mansion, Dr. Albert E. Casey / Side B: Albert E. Casey, Reginald Nessmith, Conference at Home, 1973 August 26; 94.1.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (C) Both Sides: Voluntary Family Planning, Steril Bonus, Tax adverse, Reginald Nessmith System against IQ Re Leeds, Loose Ends, R.N. on job com.Act. War on Poverty, Mayor James MCA, Foldup Elect., Re Mrs. D. and Local Press, R.N. on [signat], $ [On. Dix?], 1973 August 26; 94.1.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Frank McGurk, Bill Loeb, McFadden Adv. - Journal, City Ed. of J., Panels/ Side B: Panels Library, Panels, Adventuring Journal, 1973 August 26; 94.1.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T,C) Side A: Pennington, Ex. Sec. Wallace, Dr. Ross, Mrs. Wane, Dr. Albert Casey / Side B: Yarborough, [Dorough] lunch, 1973 August 27-28; 94.1.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T,C) Cont. Dr. Albert Casey, Birminghman News, Troxler Chinese lunch (to end), 1973 August 28; 94.1.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T, C) Side A: Troxler to Airport, Margaret Kelly, Napa, Bohannan[?] / Side B: Ray Bohannan, Dudley Kirk conference on offset, 1973 August 28-September 24; 94.1.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Brownstein, Hud, Jim Davis, Mrs. Yates, ELS MC, Beverly Taylor, Birmingham, Ala. News / Side B: Beverley Taylor, Stallworth, Frank Truchon, Birm. News, Parets, 1973 August 29; 94.1.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Parets, Talbott Kendall Jr., Wang, Ray Bohannon / Side B: Bohannon KKIS, [No Ans], Hal Parets, Tapes of McGrady, 1973 August 29- September 1; 94.1.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Parets, Sandy Froman re Bohannon, KKIS / Side B: Parets, KKIS, Program Ray Bohannon, Feinstein etc., 1973 September 2; 94.1.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: KKIS, Bohannon, Parets, Wang / Side B: Parets & Wang, KROIV Levy, Gill Ayesha, Don Worden, Joseph White, 1973 September 2-5; 94.1.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Ernie Smith #1 Call #2 Diamond / Side B: Dr. Saltman, 1973 September 4-9; 94.1.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Yarborough, Cooklin, KRON, Sen. Domaids Asst. Valentine / Side B: Brownstein Hod, Al Wang, KPIX, Jen Davies, Hal Parets, 1973 September 8; 94.2.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV) Side A: In Studio TV Speak Out Ch 7 Dave, Valentine, DW on debates / Side B: [Bus & Fin?], KRON, 1973 September 7; 94.2.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Hal Parets / Side B: Parets, Parets re list of NAS, 1973 September 8; 94.2.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Tp) Side A: #1 - Dr. Geo. Mandler, #2 - Prof. Davidson, #3 - ESAU, #4 - Hardin 1&2 / Side B: #1 - Hardin, #2 - White not IN-SVS, #3 - J. White, 1973 September 8-9; 94.2.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Jim Davis, Schneer, Frant, [illegible, Sloc. Tech.?] Mrs. Arnold / Side B: Mrs. Arnold, Parets re Hardin & Saltman, 1973 September 8-9; 94.2.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Parets, Orem, Goosebumps, Burst Ideas / Side B: Orem, GSL re Relf story, Ch 7 Ayesha Gill, Maynard Smith, Ralphandy (UCB), 1973 September 9; 94.2.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Ch 7, Bill [illegible], Mrs. Arnold, Mary C $, Dominick Office, Senator Woodruff / Side B: Woodruff-Dominick office, Mrs. Loeb, GSL, Termant, Bryan, Rarick, T. Bryan, Jim Davis, 1973 September 9; 94.2.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Jim Davis, Loeb, Sen. Dominick, JLJ of [illegible], Bryan, Tom Waring / Side B: Tom Waring, Al Wang, Bohannon, Brownsteing, Hud., 1973 September 11-12; 94.2.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th)Side A: Brownstein, Loeb, GSL, EMIC / Side B: GSL, Jos E. [Corklin?], John R. Rarick, GSL re Relf Cul., 1973 September 12-13; 94.2.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: ELS & Menices, Pat Foster, Tom Allan, Loeb Res. / Side B: Loeb, Dave Vallentine, Vince Berg, David Menkes, Parets re change, 1973 September 13-16; 94.2.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Prets, AR Jensen on his culture loaded tests / Side B: A.R. Jensen, Jim Davis, Mrs. Wythes [illegible], 1973 September 16; 94.2.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th, TV) Side A: Dave Valen, Ch 4 "Speak Out" Don Sorden W=S on Acr / Side B: Mrs. Wythes re [Kuivanis?], Hal Parets, 1973 September 16; 94.3.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Hal Parets, P.N. McCluskey, Bob [Beyers?], Loeb, Holstein, Barton CIT, Loeb Sec, Sandy re Hud Forum / B Side: Sandy Froman, ELS re Cho Hainstock, Gary re UCSB poll, RT Osborne re NAS, 1973 September 16-19; 94.3.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Travis Osborne, Dovrough, Schneer, Georgia Pottal, Shawlow, HP, Jim Davis, ARJ / Side B: ARJ, Jim Crow re introduce ARJ, 1973 September 19-22; 94.3.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Jim Crow, ARJ, ARJ re Harlow, RT Osborne / Side B: GSLeonard, ARJ, NAS Mrs. Crawford, Osborne re Abst., 1973 September 22-24; 94.3.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: R.T. Osborne, Parets, Dudley Kirk / Side B: SFEx, SJ Merc, Napa - Debbie McGuire, Margaret Kelly, Hal Parets, (KHJ [illegible]), 1973 September 24-25; 94.3.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: Copy Parets, Eran [Hardem?], Gary Hakn UCSB poll, KHJ / Side B: KHJ program, 1973 September 25; 94.3.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Hal Parets, Margaret Kelly, Travis Osborne, [Shulran?], USNWR, Andy Smith, FHS / Side B: Andy Smith, FH Smith, La Falette, Jack Robinson, Evelyn Clayton, Robinson, Miss La Follette, 1973 September 25-28; 94.3.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: KHJ end program, conf., River's lunch [ALL BAD] / Side B: River's Lunch, 1973 September 25; 94.3.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (VID) "80% (at 2000) IQ geneticity" Interview with press and Napa group [1/2], 1973 September 27; 94.3.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (VID) "80% (at 2000) IQ geneticity" Interview with press and Napa group [2/2], 1973 September 27; 94.3.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Miss La Follette, Fred Smith, Book Orders, FH Smith, Office, NAS, GSL / Side B: GSL re travel exp to FREE, Staten Island, Al Wang, 1973 September 28; 94.3.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Joe Jedd, Jim Gibbons re MC, Mrs. Hol: New Directions, [Birenbam?], Staton Island, Landes over / Side B: Staton Island, ELS, Wirbigler, ELS Brant, WFM/ RB, Leon and Herzenberg, 1973 October 1-5; 94.4.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T,C) Side A: Chevroff, Olkin, Roger Williams, Dan Bershader re Swopac, Lee Rothstein/ Side B: Lee Rothstein, Henry Fuchs Fresh. Seminar, Sherby lunch, 1973 October 4-18; 94.4.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Herzenberg, Hilary Hanon, Calhoun, F. Mc, Winbigler, Dave Fulton, Sherby / Side B: Sherby, Brownstein, [Hoel?] Law Forum, 1973 October 5-6; 94.4.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) Academic Council on W=S Resolution, Holman Patio, 1973 October 5; 94.4.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Brownstein, Halstein, Fuchs, Miller, Census Bureau, Dr. Ono / Side B: Ono, Census Bureau, Goddard, M.C., [Breinerstock?], Wang gets Mag. Res, 1973 October 6-9; 94.4.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: A.V. Scott, [Agrie?], W = S ahead courage, Parets, Virginia / Side B: End Arness, 1973 October 8-9; 94.4.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Al Wang, Jack Hoffman, Roth Occidental, Census Bureau, Bob Simragi, Census, Rence Miller / Side B: GSL, Kenneth Sharp, Jack Hoffman re Mary C, 1973 October 9-10; 94.4.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) IE3 - Engineers in SF, Inv. Trstr-Ex-CFM, Jack Shulman, 1973 October 9; 94.4.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Fred Smith: Smith-Berg, Smith-Parets, Smith-Shockley, Smith-Holstein, Smith-Scott, Smith-Parets, Smith-Arness, 1973 October 10-11; 94.4.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Jack Hofman, Office ECS re $, Fundraisers, Kenneth Sharp, Fred Smith / Side B: Dr. Jim Lucier Senator Holms office, Ten. Bryan Office, Sen. Dominick's office Woodruff, 1973 October 10-12; 94.4.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Domenick office, Leadership Conference, McCloskey office, Tennant B, R.T. Osborne / Side B: OSborne, Mrs. K Sharp, Mrs. Troxler, Fred Smith, Wrong Number, 18-year old Richard [illegible], 1973 October 12-13; 94.4.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Wrong Number, Richard [Corvein?], Troxler, A.R. Jensen / Side B: ARJ re NAS etc., Kenneth Sharp, 94.4.12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Kenneth Sharp, Loeb Res, Tennant Bryan, Doris Hapgood, Travis Daugan, Hud Crimson, Hud Marshall/ Side B: David [Brendngy?], Daugan, Bob Beyers, Hud Crimson, Schneer, [Emarru?] - El, Geo Leonard re Hud Crimson, 1973 October 14-16; 94.5.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: GSL, Karen Klinga, NUL Doris, Mark Rozen, SUD, [Reib?] Jaroslovksy / Side B: Jaroslovsky, Fred Smith, Hernstein re Crimson, 1973 October 16; 94.5.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Hernstein, SUPD, Hud Crimson, MUL Tibbets Check Levon, Side B: Reibman re MC$, ARJ, $MC P.R. & J. Hofman, RJ Hofman, G.S.L. re Wald, Levonstein, 1973 October 16-17; 94.5.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) GSL re Levontin, R.W. Sullivan, [Herrnstein?] / Side B: Herrnstein re coop., Correl., Shapiro Brownstein, MUL Tibbets, 1973 October 17-18; 94.5.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) Emanu-El, S.J. Cal Schneer, 1973 October 17; 94.5.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) Debate W=S, Cavalli-Sforza, 1973 October 17; 94.5.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: CORE, Helms-Lucier, Tom Waring, CORE, Bob Beyers / Side B: CORE, Mann, Pete McClo[rhen?], Bob Beyers, Boston Sullivan, Ralph Warner Sullivan, 1973 October 18; 94.5.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Ralph Sullivan, Weintrob Boston Globe, Jeff Leonard, Hud Crimson, Ralph Sullivan / Side B: Ralph Sullivan, WU to Levontin, Jaroslovsky & Innis-Dennisan, Bill Johnson KZSU, Roth, 1973 October 18; 94.5.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Roth, Osborne, Barb Jensen, ARJ, CORE Dennison, McFarland-McClosky, Oren, Ralph Sullivan on Wald, H.F.W, McKay NBC in NY, 1973 October 18-19; 94.5.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: McKay NBC - NY, Susskind Shows, Stern, McClosky, Askmore, Ravick / Side B: Tennak Bryan, G.S.L., [Miks?] Culbert, Osborne, GSL on Wald & Block Cancus, 1973 October 19-20; 94.6.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: GSL, Raplh Sullivan, WO to Wald, Lehner, Barosa / Side B: ARJ, ARJ, Whig-Clio, Reg. Orem, 1973 October 20- November 11; 94.6.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) Block [Audio], Contrib. Papers, ARJ, 1973 October 22; 94.6.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Overmann NSF, Mike Culbert, MUL Ferriter, V. Club Lounge G.S., DS, ARJ, TO, RO / Side B: V. [Lorenze?], 1973 October 22; 94.6.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) Cannon House Conference W=S Resol. NAS, McClosky Office, Rarick Office, 1973 October 23; 94.6.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - ARJ on Sch. Qual., 1973 October 23; 94.6.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Mike Culbert, ELS, Susskind Show, Sam Zurich, Gene Kennedy / Side B: Susskind Show, Ralph Sullivan, 1973 October 23-24; 94.6.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: ELS, Hutchings, LIT Eng & Sci, Zurich. Susskind, / Side B: RJH, Debbie Weinstein ASU, Dennison, Innes, Hud Crimson, Meislin & Vicky Wells, 1973 October 24-25; 94.6.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Vicky Wells, Hud Crimson, Zurich, Susskind / Side B: Viola Lewis (John W. Money), Innis-Dennison, Barosa (Matrola), 1973 October 25-26; 94.6.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV, T) Side A: Barosa, Hud Crimson, Iver Peterson NYT, Baker, Susskind TP / Side B: David Susskind Program - 1&2 of 3, 1973 October 26-29; 94.6.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV, T) Side A: Susskind Show (3 of 3) / Side B: Dan Noble (Neg IQ, Model, Re HQPRT), 1973 October 29-30; 94.6.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Harry C. Hart, Debbie Weinstein, U of W, Iver Peterson NYT, ASUW, Debbie Weinstein, / Side B: Wtu. of W.U., Fred Smith, M. Shepard Princeton, D[illegible], CSUSD Byron King, 1973 October 30- November 2; 94.7.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Suburban Clerk, R.J. Herrnstein, James Miller, University of Michigan, GSL / Side B: Whig-Clio, McKay NBC, D Weinstein, after her [illegible], McKay "Tomorrow" NBC, GSL, Bill Loeb MUL, 1973 Nov 3-7; 94.7.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T,C) Side A: Race Relations Report, VAL, NY to Seattle, Magazine/ Side B: Melville (Solomon), Go[illegible], Sch[illegible], ASUW, D.W., 1973 Nov 7-8; 94.7.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (D) Associated Students of the University of Washington (ASUW) Debate, 1973 Nov 8; 94.7.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (D) Associated Students of the University of Washington (ASUW) Debate Cont., 1973 November 8; 94.7.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Decision for Debate #2, Smoot, Tomorrow Show, Debbie Weinstein, E>W> re sign on #2, GSH, Daily, Debbie Weinstein, 1973 Nov 8-9; 94.7.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L,T) ACLU (American Civil Liberties Union), W=S Lecture (Side 1&2 of 4), Dick Pacisson, Spitter, Vote on Spitter, 1973 Nov 9; 94.7.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) W=S Lecture (Sides 3&4 of 4), 1973 Nov 9; 94.7.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV, T, C) Side A: Ralph [Boyard?] / Side B: Birenbaum, Stat, Noreen, Glen, Knute Anderson, Note after telephone Karl Marinez, Buckley, TV Herrstein, Bever, 94.7.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV) Channel 9 Buckley, Herrnstein, 1973 Nov 11; 94.7.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: OREM re Whig, ARJ tape, KUOW re tape / Side B: [Cancro?], GSL, Ellis Page, Western Union, 1973 Nov 11; 94.7.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: W.U. Blanshard, U of Connecticut, GSL, A.R.J. KUOW, RHW, NBC DC / Side B: NBG Gannon, GSL re poster, Bill Loeb, Blanshard (Rufus), U of Connecticut, 1973 Nov 11-12; 94.8.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Blanshard, Conn. Campus Daily, SU Daily, Al Wang, Julia Cline, Hud Crimson / Side B: Julia Cline, Hud Crimson, Paul Bevosa, GSL re T, Dan Noble, ARJ re SDS release, IBM, Al Wang, 1973 Nov 12-14; 94.8.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Al Wang, Iver Peterson, Bill Loeb, Tomorrow McKay, Warren Steibel, Blanshard Home / Side B: Blanshard, Bud Hall, NY Times, Bill Loeb, Norwalk, Paul Soloman "Real Paper", 1973 Nov 14-15; 94.8.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Solomon "Real Paper", Holmstrom / Side B: Hartford Courant, Bob Beyers, Fidele[goes?], Karmel Courant, Washingon Square Daily News, Chris Chang, 1973 Nov 15; 94.8.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Chris Chang, Brennan Australian Broadcast Communications (Sydney) / Side B: Paul Barosa, Weyher, Loeb Hall, Mrs. Maggin, Chancellor Sidney Borowitz, 1973 Nov 15-16; 94.8.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Pat Sexton, Loeb, Chris Chang, Leonard Gal / Side B: Blanshard, Landex, Terese Karmel, IBM, Crocker Angloss, 1973 Nov 16; 94.8.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: H.F. Weyer, Loeb, Kendric, [illegible] / Side B: Marshall Conn. Sunday Herald, Brienbaum, Weyher, 1973 Nov. 16-20; 94.8.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV, C) Side A: / KPIX Date, interview Alan Burkey, Side B: KPIX Alan Burke, HFW, Sheldon Englemayer, Jim Gannon NBC, KPIC Scotti, ST. Is. Com. Coll. Kriestman, 1973 Nov. 19; 94.8.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: WCBS Dabe Lenan Interview, Crump Princeton / Side B: Paul Kern, 1973 Nov 19-20; 94.8.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (Th) Side A: Kendrix, Smith, [illegible], Berza, [illegible] / Side B: Fox "Tomorrow" NBC Next, 1973 Nov 20-Dec 10; 94.8.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (D, C, T) Side A: Crump, Princeton Packet, Cahrley Bennet, KZSU & WCBS Daniel Dhoe, Seymore Hirsch / Side B: Start Debate, 1973 Nov 20; 94.8.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T,D) Side A: cont Leppe, Bevers, Face Reality, Talk Racism, Let you speak, [illegible], W=S at BB / Side B: S to FW dandy job, [Nazi at me?], RI If W=S on P.S., Chris Kendrick SU Daily, FW on genetic apology, 1973 Nov 20-21; 94.9.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: GSL, Rose, Gannon NBC, Ms. Suzanne [St. Piene?], CBS Morning news / Side B: Cont CBS Morning News, Mary Dennison CORE, 1973 Nove 21; 94.9.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (C,T) Side A: Cennison CORE, Ch 5 on W=S, [Paul Kerns?] / Side B: Whig-Clio, N. AM Newspaper Alliance, Ron [Secrest?] re H-W, 1973 Nov 21-24; 94.9.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: Coon checks acc, Rudda Sp. / Side B: [Engelyeir?] NANA, WCBS, LANDO CBS, 1973 Nov 25-26; 94.9.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV) Side A: WCBS Morn. News, INNIS / Side B: Welsing 1 of 2, LANDO CBS, D.C. NBC, 1973 Nov 26-27; 94.9.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: WELSING / Side B: Studio, Lando, Hart [Princetonian?], ASI, CBS, WNBC, 1973 Nov 27; 94.9.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: WOR, Winkler, [Bossa Phoenix?], Whig Cleo, BTL [illegible] / Side B: Whig Clio, Hart, Engelmayor, NAS, [Callchon?], Phoenix TW, Inv. Trstr ECFM Motorola, 1973 Nov 27-29; 94.9.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L) Side A: Motorola Side B: Motorola, 1973 Nov 29; 94.9.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (L,C,T) Side A: End Motorola Lect, Zielenziger, Paul Taylor, Philadelphia Inquirer cover up, [illegible] / Side B: Paul Taylor, Phil Enquirer, Princetonia Zielenziger, Engelmayer, John Jay Col., Peddle at Barosa, AAL to EWR, 1973 Nov 29-1973 Dec 1; 94.9.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T,C) Side A: AAL Phoenix to D.C. to Nak, Tape, Demps, Bennett, FK, Gold Rl. / Side B: Chas. Bennett, Paul Jacobs, Whig-Chio Sheperd, Hod Crimson Julia Kline + Lemon, 1973 Dec 1-3; 94.9.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: Bennett + Reed Mc[Cludidge?] Hartford [Courant?], Iver Peterson, Weintraub B.Glb, Lemon Hod C, Teresa Karmel / Side B: Lando, Bruce McKay, Princetorian DZ, Handler Whig, Ny Dly News, Parker WOR cont., 1973 Dec 3; 94.9.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (C,T) Side A: Parker WOR, Robert Reinhold NYT, TIME (N.G.), Steve Duncan NYDN re (back cop?), 14=10P+4F Shepard, Karen Winkler, Innes, Handler / Side B: Ada Byrnes, Handler, Press conf underway, 1973 Dec 3-4; 94.10.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (C,D) Side A: Press Conf, Bruce McKay, Bressler, [McCosh?] / Side B: [Bressles Indro W=S?], Mike Preschool,6 Prof S says "not racist", 1973 Dec 4; 94.10.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (D) Side A: A.M. applause, WHIG-CLIO Shockley / Side B: IND? REK Hotel, 1973 Dec 4; 94.10.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: Whig [Dennith?] / Side B: Adams Wst, 1973 Dec 4; 94.10.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: Jim Adams Wst J (Teaham), Notes, CBS News, [Monsky?], NY Times, NET, [Spivak?] Meet Press / Side B: Spivak MP, WABC Brownstein, SMCA, Whig, NYT, AP, WOR, Bill Loeb re Barry[ Earber?], 1973 Dec 4-5; 94.10.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (R, T) Side A: Bill Loeb, Barry [Farber?] WOR, Levy?, Late tape start on WOR barry Farber Blast, [illegible] / Side B: WOR, 1973 Dec 5; 94.10.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (R, T) Side A: Kroll, Bob; J.P. Morgan; Jeffry Troy; WWRG; Ch 7; Carch WMCA; Bob Grant / SIde B: WMCA, Mrs. Nobile, Kroll, Brownstein Segall, 1973 Dec 5-6; 94.10.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: Rabinow; Philip Nobile; D. Mitra re C-FM; Landro CBS; Boethe [Muzk?] / Side B: Boethe, Richards Newsweek; Dim Ret, [illegible], 1973 Dec 6; 94.10.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: Boethe Newsweek, Regression IIG / Side B: Boethe, Schizo ELS, Toni Ehrlich, WWLR Clemons, 1973 Dec 6; 94.10.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV) Dr. Shockley WABC-TV, 1973 Dec 7; 94.10.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Post AM at WABC, Richard Boeth Newsweek / Side B: Nobile at LaG, 19763 Dec 7; 94.10.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: Nobile, Bruce McKay, Bob + Rose Kroll at Chic Airport / Side B: NBC Fox, Sunny Fox Conf, Cards, Picasso, Lunch Innes Suite, 1973 Dec 7-10; 94.11.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (TV) Side A: Tomorrow Show / Side B: Tomorrow Show, 1973 Dec 10; 94.11.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - Side A: In NBC Studio, Roger [illegible], Debate Chuck Thompson, Fred Smith or KCBS UP / Side B: KTTV, [illegible], Innis, 1973 Dec 10-14; 94.11.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)
      - (T) Side A: "Tomorrow" Fox, Rob McConnell, Ribakove, Ivy Lee, Laura [Wegher?], [illegible], Fred Smith / Side B: Fred Smith, Global TV Toronto, Warren Steibel, 1973 Dec 10-13; 94.11.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 94)